(Leonard:)Probably because
I exude confidence.
(Leonard:)People are drawn to that,
you know?
(Leonard:)Confidence, not exuding.
(Page:)Do you know of any groups
Mr. Wolowitz is a member of?
(Leonard:)You are beautiful,
(Leonard:)you know that?
(Leonard:)You pop, sparkle
and buzz electric.
(Leonard:)I'm going to pick you up
at 8:00,
(Leonard:)show you a night
you will never forget.
(Page:)Sounds great.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Raj:)Yeah.
(Page:)Can my six-foot-two Navy SEAL
husband come with us?
Is that...?
(Leonard:)Oh, my, I didn't see the ring
with my glasses off, so...
(Leonard:)Look at that,
I'm starting to exude.
(Leonard:)Want to get that?
(Sheldon:)Not particularly.
(Leonard:)Could you get that?
(Sheldon:)I suppose I could
if I were asked.